artsfon.com 2019-03-09

# Artsfon USA Privacy Policy

**Artsfon Privacy policy**

At Artsfon Wallpapers and Pictures, we put our customers first and take pride in offering our customers services that meet their individual needs. We appreciate the trust our customers have in Artsfon Wallpapers and Pictures and place the highest priority on our customers' privacy. As a Artsfon Wallpapers and Pictures customer, you can count on responsible treatment of any personal information you share with us. 

Use, Collection and Retention of Customer Information  
We collect, retain and use individual customer information ONLY when we reasonably believe it would be useful, and allowable by law, to administer to our business needs in providing products, services and other opportunities to our customers. 

This is how we handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site. If you visit our site to read information, such as consumer brochures or press releases: 

We will collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or earthlink.net if you are connecting from an earthlink account), the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. 

We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

E-Commerce Information:  
If you order products or services directly from our website, we may collect sensative payment information such as credit card numbers or checking account information. Any such information, when submitted via this website, is only collected, transmitted and/or maintained in a certified, secure environment using 128bit encryption. With on-line transaction processing, this information will be securely transmitted to our payment gateway to effect the approval and transfer of funds. With off-line transaction processing, we limit the access to that information as stated below.

If you identify yourself by sending an E-mail:   
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message. We will use that information to respond to the inquiry and provide accurate information of any questions. We will not use such information beyond the basis of the inquiry. We will not forward any such information to any third party unless required to do so by law. 

We want to be very clear: we will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. 

Maintenance of Accurate Information  
We have established procedures to ensure our customer's information is accurate, current and complete in accordance with reasonable business standards. We also respond to requests to correct inaccurate information or delete any personal information in a timely manner. 

Limiting Employee Access to Information  
We limit our employee's access to personally identifiable customer information. Further, our employees must have a valid business reason for knowing such information. We educate our employees so they understand the importance of customer confidentiality, privacy and security. We also take appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce employee privacy responsibilities. 

Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures  
We maintain rigorous security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information. 

Restrictions on the Disclosure of Account Information  
We do not reveal customer account or other personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use. However, we may exchange information with reputable reporting agencies to maximize the accuracy and security of the information. Additional exceptions that we must honor on behalf of our customers include: 

Providing information to help complete a customer initiated transaction. Responding to a customer's formal request to disclose their own account information Disclosing information that is required by/or allowed by law (e.g. subpoena; the investigation of fraudulent activity). 

Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Third Parties  
Whenever we provide customer information to a third party, we insist that the third party adhere to similar privacy principles for keeping such information confidential.   
San Jose, CA 95103  
USA
